Gourmet Detective is a tv movie, mystery film directed by Scott Smith.
Famed culinary consultant Henry Ross is a charming
food industry insider in San Francisco.
When suspicious  sabotage ends in a shocking murder at his friend’s five-star restaurant, Henry is
put on the case with strong-willed  police detective and single mom, Maggie Price.
Despite Maggie’s protests, they must work together to decipher  the clues
and investigate all of San Francisco’s top culinary pros.
Henry Ross, played by Dylan Neal.
Maggie, played by Brooke Burns.
Abigail, played by Alissa Skovbye.
Sally Aldridge, played by Kimberley Sustad.
Munro, played by Matthew Kevin Anderson.
Bailey, played by Marc Senior.
Gourmet Detective is a series of made-for-television mystery films based on a book series of the same name from author Peter King
that stars Dylan Neal as Henry Ross, a chef turned culinary sleuth and Brooke Burns as Detective Maggie Price.
Set in San Francisco, it airs on Hallmark Movies & Mysteries in the US.
The film explores themes of mother, chess, detective, murder, chef.
The tone is mind_bending.